The project name is "Sorcerer's Siege" and the project background is "In a kingdom full of magical and dangerous things, the players need to defend the kingdom as a magical role to avoid the barrages unleashed by the evil wizard."
And then this are the dangerous things such as fireball, iceball, magical ball, water ball, and snowball. And this is the player.
The CSV files with comma in their names will not be incorrectly identified when adding enemies. Entering enemy's speed will prompt an error if it is not a number or an integer.
The game will not be able to identify the player.
And add an edit or edit temporarily and are not written to the CSV file.
Click "Save" to write the file to the CSV file. Then "Delete" is "Delete".
This save is the standard for outstanding data persistence.
Finish the program by clicking "Save" and open the "Enemies.csv" to show the enemies you just added called commas and double quotes.
These are double quotes and this is "a". And then start again to see that their names are displayed correctly.
For enemy names, Speed Maps implements CRUD function with a graphical interface.
Then click "Start". Enter double quotes and commas in the name to prove the robustness of the code. Then enter decimals and letters in the velocity. A window will pop up.
After a few clicks on the drop-down box of the picture.
Selecting this enemy is selecting the corresponding tile. Before clicking to start the game, enemies will randomly send a new one from the list of existing enemies.
Then what we have to do is manipulate the player to avoid the fireball, waterball, magic ball and so on.
Then we click "Start Game".
And then this is "Restart Game"
We can also pause the game.
And then continue.
Pause and continue.
If we meet the enemy, the game is over and we can see the score on the screen.
If the ball crosses the bottom line, it scores. And for every 10 points, the difficulty level increases by 1 level and enemies become faster.
And then this is the whole game.